(Beverley:)If you want to have intercourse with that
girl, find out what cologne her father wore.
(Leonard:)Good to see you, mother.
(Leonard:)Here's your tea, mother.
- Oolong?
- Yes.
- Loose, not bagged?
- Steeped three minutes? Two-percent milk?
- Yes. Yes.
- Warmed separately?
- Yes.
- One teaspoon sugar? Raw sugar?
- Yes. Yes.
(Beverley:)It's cold.
(Leonard:)I'll start again.
(Sheldon:)I have the same problem with him.
(Sheldon:)My theory is that his lack of focus
stems from an over-developed sex drive.
Oh, I don't know where he got that.
Aside from a pro-forma consummation
of our marriage...
(Beverley:)...his father and I only had intercourse
for the purposes of reproduction.